{
    "subject": "resource/Take_Away_(song)",
    "predicate": "ontology/musicalArtist",
    "object": "resource/Missy_Elliott",
    "human_readable": "The musical artist behind the song 'Take Away' is Missy Elliott.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9148615598678589,
            "question": "Who is the musical artist behind the song 'Take Away'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7727474570274353,
            "question": "What is the name of the song performed by Missy Elliott?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7294309735298157,
            "question": "Name a famous song by Missy Elliott."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7257964015007019,
            "question": "Is Missy Elliott known for her music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.674321711063385,
            "question": "What genre of music is often associated with Missy Elliott?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6175903677940369,
            "question": "Is Missy Elliott known for her unique music style?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5740698575973511,
            "question": "What are some of Missy Elliott's other popular songs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3751087486743927,
            "question": "Has Missy Elliott won any awards for her music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37279626727104187,
            "question": "What makes 'Take Away' a memorable song?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34013545513153076,
            "question": "When was the song 'Take Away' released?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The musical artist behind the song 'Take Away' is Missy Elliott.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8675_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What makes 'Take Away' a memorable song?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8675_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Missy Elliott won any awards for her music?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8675_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of Missy Elliott's other popular songs?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8675_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8675_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8675_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8675_118.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8675_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8675_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8675_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8675_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8675_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8675_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8675_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents mention \"Missy Elliott\" in relation to the song \"Take Away,\" indicating she is the musical artist behind it."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "\"Take Away\" is a song by Missy Elliott, but the context information provided does not explicitly state that she was the artist behind it. It mentions that the video contains images of Aaliyah and lyrics about her memory, which suggests that the song could be one of Aaliyah's songs as it was released after her death in 2001. Missy Elliott co-wrote \"Take Away\" for Aaliyah, but it was not a solo song by Missy.",
            "category": 4
        }
    }
}